Guide to the Terry Sanford Papers, 1926-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Constituent Services Series, 1986-1992 and undated
  - Correspondence Management System Subseries, 1987-1988.
    - 1988, Mar. 15-Nov. 26, (7 folders) (Box 19)
  - Replies to Constituents Subseries, 1987-1992
    Photocopies of Sanford's replies to constituents on personal and public matters. Includes condolences, regrets, congratulations, and thank-you notes for gifts, campaign contributions, and support.
    - 1987, Jan. -July 17, (12 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1987, July 20-1988, Sept., (24 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1988, Oct. -1989, Dec. 18, (20 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1989, Dec. 19-1991, Jan. 16, (20 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1991, Jan. 17-1992, July, (28 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1992, Aug.-1992, Dec.8, (6 folders) (Box 24)
    - Constituent Cases, 1992, July-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 24)
- Personal/Political, 1985-1992
  The Personal/Political series is divided into the following subseries: General Correspondence; Personal Correspondence; Correspondence Subject Files; Budget; Campaign; Appointment Books; Memoranda; Nominations; Advisory Board; Invitations; and Personal Journals.
  - General Correspondence Subseries, 1987-1992
    General Correspondence Subseries consists of formal letters between Sanford and constituents, corporations, foundations, acquaintances, and colleagues.
    Arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by correspondent's last name.
    - A, 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 25)
    - Agriculture, 1986 (Box 25)
    - American Dance Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - Answer file, 1989 (Box 25)
    - The Asia Society- Williamsburg Conference, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Aspen Institute Conference, Jamaica, 1987 (Box 25)
    - August Recess, Switzerland, 1987 (Box 25)
    - B-C, 1988-1922, (10 folders) (Box 25)
    - C, 1988-1992, (8 folders) (Box 26)
    - Condolence letters, 1990 (Box 26)
    - Condolences/Illnesses, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Congratulatory letters, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Congratulations, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - D, 1987-1992, (5 folders) (Box 26)
    - Duke University: (Box 27)
      - 1987-1989, (5 folders) (Box 27)
      - Admissions, 1988-1922, (5 folders) (Box 27)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 27)
    - Duke-Dingell matter, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - E, 1987-1992, (4 folders) (Box 27)
    - Eagle Scout, 1988-1992, (18 folders) (Box 28)
    - Eli Evans/ Judah Benjamin: Reception, 1988 (Box 28)
    - F-H, 1987-1992, (17 folders) (Box 29)
    - H-M, 1987-1992, (23 folders) (Box 30)
    - M-R, 1987-1992, (21 folders) (Box 31)
    - Recommendations, 1987-1991, (7 folders) (Box 32)
    - Student recommendations, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - S, 1987-1992, (7 folders) (Box 32)
    - Science policy, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Staff information, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
    - T, 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 33)
    - Thank-you's:
      - (Christmas cards, gifts, etc.), 1991 (Box 33)
      - Sent, 1990 (Box 33)
      - Received, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - U, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - U.S. Senate, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - V-W, 1987-1992, (8 folders) (Box 33)
    - W, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - 1983-1991, (10 folders) (Box 34)
  - Personal Correspondence Subseries, 1985-1990
    Personal Correspondence Subseries includes correspondence regarding contributions; congratulations; thank-you notes; and personal letters from Sanford to friends, supporters, and colleagues.
    - A-H, 1989-1990, (16 folders) (Box 35)
    - H-M, 1985-1990, (20 folders) (Box 36)
    - M-R, 1985-1990, (24 folders) (Box 37)
    - S-W, 1985-1989, (20 folders) (Box 38)
    - W-Z, 1985-1990, (9 folders) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence Subject Files Subseries, 1986-1992
    Files containing correspondence from interest groups, constituents, and colleagues expressing their opinions on particular issues.
    Arranged alphabetically by issue and organization.
    - Adams, McCullough and Beard, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Aging Committee, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Agriculture, 1989 (Box 40)
    - AID-Foreign Aid, 1990 (Box 40)
    - Air Force, 1992 (Box 40)
    - All-China Youth Federation, 1987 (Box 40)
    - American Bar Association, 1992 (Box 40)
    - American Business Conference, 1989 (Box 40)
    - American Council of Young Political Leaders, 1987-1989 (Box 40)
    - American Dance Festival, 1990-1992 (Box 40)
    - American Institute for Public Service, 1989-1990 (Box 40)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
    - St. Andrews interview, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Announcements received, 1987-1990 (Box 40)
    - Araskog, Rand (ITT), 1990 (Box 40)
    - Aspen Institute: General, 1989-1992 (Box 40)
    - Auction requests, 1987-1990 (Box 40)
    - Awards received, 1990 (Box 40)
    - Baker, James A, III (Dept. of State), 1989 (Box 40)
    - Bason, George Francis Jr. ( U.S. Bankruptcy Court Reappointment), 1988-1989 (Box 40)
    - Ben Sutton Golf Course, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Bicentennial Resolution, 1991-1992 (Box 40)
    - BIFAB (Flowers and Lavery), 1990-1991 (Box 40)
    - Bill of Rights Day, 1989-1991 (Box 40)
    - Billington, James (Library of Congress), 1992 (Box 40)
    - Bodne, Ben: Memorial, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Bowman-Gray, 1988-1992 (Box 40)
    - Boyles, Harlan, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Brandeis University, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Brookings Institution/Member's Directory, 1988-1992 (Box 40)
    - Brown, Bill: Nomination, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Bush, James H., 1988 (Box 40)
    - Cable TV, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Cambodia: Testimony by Senator J. Robert Kerrey, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Cadmus Communications Corporation, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Camnus, Fred, 1987-1989 (Box 40)
    - Campaign Reform:
      - 1989-1990 (Box 40)
      - Campaign Expenditures, S.2, 1988-1989 (Box 40)
      - Campaign Finance Reform, S.Res.70, 1992 (Box 40)
      - Democratic Freshman letter, 1989, Jan.25 (Box 40)
      - Responses from members regarding nominating process, 1990 (Box 40)
      - S.377, Eight Regional Presidential, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Canadian Trade Mission, 1988, Sept. (Box 40)
    - Cappello, Juan C. (ITT), 1991 (Box 40)
    - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology and Government, 1990-1991 (Box 40)
    - Carnes, Ed: Nomination, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Carolina Museum of Contemporary Art, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
    - Carrington, Paul (article), 1992 (Box 41)
    - Carter, Gilmer; WWI Vets, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
    - Carter project, 1991-1992 (Box 41)
    - Catastrophic Health Care, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
    - Census, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Chamber of Commerce Groups, 1989-1992 (Box 41)
    - Charlotte Motor Speedway, undated (Box 41)
    - Charlotte Observer: Letter to Him Morrill, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Children's Home Society of North Carolina, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Christ School, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
    - Citizens Conferences, 1988-1990 (Box 41)
    - Citizens Forums, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
    - Civil Societies, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Clark Equipment Company, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Clean Air Legislation, 1989 (Box 41)
    - Coalition for Democratic Values ( Howard Metzenbaum's group), 1990 (Box 41)
    - Cochrane, Bill; Committee on Rusles/Administration, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Commemorative coins, 1989 (Box 41)
    - Commemorative Stamp: Issued, 1989, Aug.22 (Box 41)
    - Commission on National Challenges in High Education, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Concerned Senators for the Arts, 1987-1991 (Box 41)
    - Condolence/Illness notes, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Conference Board, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Congratulations, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Congressional Caucuses, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Congressional Study Group on Germany, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Congressional University Colloquium, 1989 (Box 41)
    - Constitution cards for schools, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Contra Aid, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1987-1992 (Box 41)
    - Council on Foundations, 1990-1992 (Box 41)
    - Crime Bill, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Department of Defense correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 41)
    - Discovery Place, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Dixon, Rodney, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Drew, Thomas, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Drugs, Drug Report-Interns, 1983-1990 (Box 41)
    - The Duke Endowment, 1989-1991 (Box 41)
    - Duke Alumni: Contacts, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Duke University:
      - Aging in Black Americans Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 41)
      - Canadian Studies Center, 1989-1991 (Box 41)
      - Clark Cahow's Board/Canadian Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 41)
      - Class of 1989 Reunion, 1990 (Box 41)
      - John bequest/ Staclean Diffuser Co., 1986 (Box 41)
      - Medical Center, 1990-1992 (Box 41)
    - Duke Club of Washington, 1989 (Box 41)
    - Duke Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1990 (Box 41)
    - Duke International Business Education and Research, 1992 (Box 41)
    - Duke Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Duke; The Phantom of the Opera, 1991 (Box 42)
    - Duke pledges, 1991 (Box 42)
    - Duke University: The Private Adjudication Center, 1990 (Box 42)
    - Duke Projects, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Duke Public Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 42)
    - Durham Arts Council, 1988 (Box 42)
    - Durham, 1987-1990 (Box 42)
    - Department of State (Lawrence S. Eagleburger), 1989, Sept.-1992, Sept. (Box 42)
    - East Carolina University, 1992, Oct. (Box 42)
    - Economic Recovery Leader, DPC Plan, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Economic Recovery, 1991, Oct.-1992, Mar., (5 folders) (Box 42)
    - Education:
      - 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 42)
      - Background paper on higher education, 1987 (Box 42)
      - Columns, 1991, May (Box 42)
      - Columns and general, 1991 (Box 42)
      - Column: Is Choice a Choice?, 1991, July (Box 42)
      - Commission Seminars, 1990, Dec.-1991, Sept. (Box 42)
      - DPC (Democratic Policy Committee) reports, 1991 (Box 42)
      - Department of Secretary of Education correspondence, 1991, Mar.-1992, Mar. (Box 42)
      - Governor's project, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
      - Letter to former governors/responses, 1990 (Box 42)
      - President Bush, 1991 (Box 42)
      - School Project, 1992, June (Box 42)
      - Spanking in schools, 1991,Apr. (Box 42)
      - Teach for America, 1990 (Box 42)
      - Young Black Men in America Project, 1990 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 42)
    - Elizabeth II (Queen), 1991 (Box 42)
    - Eno River Valley, 1988, July-Dec. (Box 42)
    - Esperanto, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
    - European Economic Community (EEC):
      - 1989-1992 (Box 42)
      - Background materials, 1988-1992 (Box 42)
      - General, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 42)
      - Proposal for America Sponsors, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Eli Evans tribute, 1991, Nov.-1992, Jan. (Box 42)
    - Executive Mansion Fine Arts Committee, 1991, Jan. (Box 42)
    - Fayetteville, North Carolina, 1989 (Box 43)
    - FBI (Federal Bureau of Investigation) file, 1990-1992 (Box 43)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Federal Election Commission, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Federal Reserve System, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Gans, Curtis B.; Committee for the Study of the American Electorate, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Garamend, John: Statement, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Germany-U.S. Association of former members of Congress: Study group, 1989-1990 (Box 43)
    - Gifts file, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Glaxo, Inc., 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - Goddard, Sam and Judy, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Golf, Robert Trent Jones, 1986-1991 (Box 43)
    - Grace Commission, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Graham, Billy, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Graham, Frank: Poster, Profile in Courage Award, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Paul Green Foundation, Inc., Chapel Hill, N.C., 1988-1990 (Box 43)
    - Greensboro cable vision, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Hamlet fire, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Hamner, Clay, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Happy Birthday wishes, 1991-1992 (Box 43)
    - Harassment policy, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Harper Corporation of America, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Haywood County Economic Development, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Head Start, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Health Care, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Randolph Hearst Foundation: Senate Youth Program, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
    - Henderson, David, 1988-1991 (Box 43)
    - Herring, William Dallas, 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - Highways, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Highway Bill, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Hill, Ruth Scott: Recommendation, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Hodges, Luther H., Jr., 1991 (Box 43)
    - Holiday thank-yous, 1991-1992 (Box 43)
    - Hostage file, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Housing, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Hoving, John, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation Leadership Training Seminars, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Hunt, Jim, 1988-1990 (Box 43)
    - Hunting Bill, S.2309 (to protect the right to carry out a lawful hunt), 1988 (Box 43)
    - Huntington's Disease Society of America, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Hurricane Hugo, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Iacocca, Lee: Chrysler, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 43)
    - Incidents, problems, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc., 1987 (Box 43)
    - Instituto Centroamericano de Administración de Empresas (INCAE), 1991 (Box 43)
    - Inter-American Dialogue, undated (Box 43)
    - International Language: Ted Turner letter, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Interns, undated (Box 43)
    - Interparliamentary Union, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Interstate highway: Raleigh/Research Triangle, 1991 (Box 43)
    - IPU (Inter Parliamentary Union) meeting, 1991, Nov. 19 (Box 43)
    - Ireland, 1989-1990 (Box 43)
    - Irvine Group: University of California, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Jacob K Javits Foundation, Inc., 1990(?) (Box 43)
    - Jamestown Foundation, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Jefferson Group, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Jefferson Awards, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Job Corps, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Johnson, Samuel, undated (Box 43)
    - Jonas, Nancy, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Bob Jordan Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
    - Kemp, Jack: Housing and Urban Development, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Kenan, Frank, 1992 (Box 44)
    - Kennedy, Joseph B., 1991 (Box 44)
    - Kerrey, J. Robert, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Krauthammer essay, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Kudler, Harold/Harvey, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Kuniholm, Bruce: Middle East, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Lambert, Nick, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
    - Laurinburg High School, undated (Box 44)
    - Leadership: Charlotte, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
    - Learning Channel, 1990-1992 (Box 44)
    - Lees McRae College, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Legislative accomplishments, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Li Wei Kun, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
    - Library letters (re. biographical director of Senate), 1989 (Box 44)
    - Lindsay, Lawrence B., 1991 (Box 44)
    - LTV, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Lumbee Indians, 1991-1992 (Box 44)
    - Luso-American Development Foundation, undated (Box 44)
    - MacCormac, Earl R., 1991 (Box 44)
    - Madrid-embassy, 1992 (Box 44)
    - Maps: North Carolina, 1991-1992 (Box 44)
    - McConnell, Molly, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Methodist College, 1990-1992 (Box 44)
    - Miller Center Report, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
    - Miller, George, Recommendation, 1992 (Box 44)
    - Mitchell, George, Majority Leader, 1992 (Box 44)
    - Mitsubishi Electric, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Thelonius Monk Institute, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Morton, Hugh; Grandfather Mountain, 1987-1992 (Box 44)
    - Charlie Muse case, 1991 (Box 44)
    - National Academy of public Administration, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1990 (Box 44)
    - National Advisory Council on Educational Research and Improvement, 1987 (Box 44)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor, 1987 (Box 44)
    - National Civil League, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - National Football League (NFL) meeting, Orlando, Fla., 1990, Mar.11 (Box 44)
    - National Forum on Public Service, 1990 (Box 44)
    - National Humanities Center, 1987-1992 (Box 44)
    - National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences, 1991 (Box 44)
    - National Institute of Former Governors ( Jerry Apodaca), 1990-1992 (Box 45)
    - National Institute of Municipal law Officers, 1985 (Box 45)
    - National Institute of Statistical Science, 1990 (Box 45)
    - National Rifle Association, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - National Urban League, 1991 (Box 45)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 1987 (Box 45)
    - National Young Leaders Conference, 1990 (Box 45)
    - National Youth Sports Program, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Nations Bank, 1992 (Box 45)
    - New Mexico Thank-Yous, 1989 (Box 45)
    - News and Observer (Raleigh), 1990 (Box 45)
    - News releases, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - Nixon project, 1990 (Box 45)
    - Nolan, R. K., Quality Oil Management, Inc., 1988 (Box 45)
    - Nominating Process: Letter to Mitchell/ Foley, 1990, June21 (Box 45)
    - Nominations, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Normandy - D-Day Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 45)
    - North Atlantic Assembly, 1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 45)
    - N.C. Alliance of Community Financial Institutions: Board of Directors, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges/Universities, 1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Bankers Association: Board of Directors, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1987 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Businesswomen: Honored, 1991 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Coalition for Community Action, undated (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Community Colleges, 1988-1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Council of State, 1987-1988 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina County Commissioners, 1991-1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Department of Agriculture, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Department of Transportation, 1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina: Distinguished Women Awards, 1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Economic Development Report, 1987 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Enterprise Corporation, 1989 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Furniture Manufacturers, 1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina General Assembly, 1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Governor's Office, 1989-1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Governor's Schools, 1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Highway Users Conference, 1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Humanities Council, 1990-1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Institute of Politics, 1988 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Job Corps, undated (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Leadership Forum, 1987 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Meat Packers Co., 1987 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Politics, undated (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Pork Producers Association, 1989 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Poverty Program ( George Esser), 1989-1990 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1989-1992 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina World Trade Association, 1990 (Box 45)
    - Oregon Inlet, 1988-1990 (Box 45)
    - Outward Bound, 1990-1992 (Box 45)
    - Park, Charles B. III, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Parker, Poe, Adams, and Bernstein, undated (Box 45)
    - Palton, Victoria L., 1991 (Box 45)
    - PBS information, 1991 (Box 45)
    - Pearl Harbor, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Penland School, 1987 (Box 45)
    - Pepper, Claude, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Pepper Commission, 1990 (Box 45)
    - Phelps, Jake, 1985-1986 (Box 45)
    - Phillips, A. Craig: Educational Foundation, 1988 (Box 45)
    - Phillips, J. Dickson, 1990 (Box 45)
    - Pledges:
      - Boulware Scholarship Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 45)
      - Christ School: the Plan for the 2nd Century, 1987-1989 (Box 45)
      - Council on Foreign Relations: the Campaign for the Council, 1987 (Box 45)
      - Duke University:
        - Chapel Development Fund ( Robert Young Fund), 1987 (Box 45)
        - Davison Club (Elizabeth Sanford Endowment), 1987-1989 (Box 45)
        - Friends of the Library, 1987 (Box 45)
        - Washington Duke Club, 1987 (Box 45)
      - Howard University, 1987 (Box 45)
      - N.C. Outward Bound School (Capital Funds Drive), 1987 (Box 45)
      - UNC Annual Giving Carolina Fund, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Poisson, David, 1991 (Box 45)
    - Post election correspondence, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Post election correspondence, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Powell, Colin L.: Commencement address, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Press, 1987-1992 (Box 46)
    - Psychology: Journal of Experimental Psychology article, 1980 (Box 46)
    - PUHCA (Public Utility Holding Company Act) Reform, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Rafferty-Brown, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Candis Ray vs. U.S. Senate, 1989-1991 (Box 46)
    - Recipes, undated (Box 46)
    - Recommendations, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
    - Regan, Sam, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Release forms, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Representatives, (U.S. House of), 1991-1992 (Box 46)
    - Research Triangle Park, 1990 (Box 46)
    - Rhine, J. B., 1980 (Box 46)
    - Rhyne, Charles, 1990 (Box 46)
    - R.J. Reynolds: Smokeless Cigarette materials, 1987-1990 (Box 46)
    - Roberson, Dorothy, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Roll Call newspaper, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Rural housing: North Carolina, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Sale, Jim, 1990 (Box 46)
    - Sarbanes/Sasser letter, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Albert Schweitzer prize for Humanitarianism: Johns Hopkins University, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Science and Math Bill, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Science: The End of the Frontier?, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Science facilities:
      - Higher Education Colloquium, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 46)
      - Colloquium: Bush response letters, 1990 (Box 46)
      - Colloquium/Congress, undated (Box 46)
    - Science policy:
      - 1989 (Box 46)
      - Bush letter, 1990 (Box 46)
    - Tribute to Ralph H. Scott, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Seawell, M. Buie, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Semans, James and Mary D.B.T., 1990 (Box 46)
    - U.S. Senate, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Senator to staff, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
    - Shaw Company: Ft. Bragg contract, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Shiloh True Light Church of Christ, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Sklar, Barry, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Society of International Business Fellows: Don Hughes letter, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Souter, David H., 1990 (Box 46)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Southern Stated Energy Board: Advisory Committee on TVA, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Staff to Senator, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
    - Strom Thurmond Institute, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Supreme Court: Judicial Fellows program, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Sustainable Development, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Jimmie Swartz Foundation, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Sweet Potato materials, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Taxes, 1987-1988 (Box 47)
    - Terry Sanford Teacher Award, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Tennessee, 1986-1988 (Box 47)
    - Think Tanks, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Thomas, Clarence, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Tobacco Institute, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Touro National Heritage, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Tower, John, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Treasure-America, undated (Box 47)
    - Treasury, Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 47)
    - Tree of Life, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Tributes and Testimonials, 1990 (Box 47)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 1990 (Box 47)
    - United Nations Association of the U.S.A., 1989 (Box 47)
    - United Negro College Fund, Inc., 1991 (Box 47)
    - U.S. Memories, 1989 (Box 47)
    - United Service Organizations (USO), 1988 (Box 47)
    - United States Special Operations Command, undated (Box 47)
    - University of North Carolina:
      - 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - Chancellor centennial, 1991 (Box 47)
      - Dan K. Moore program, 1987-1988 (Box 47)
      - Greensboro: Integrity in Business and Government speech (Lindberry), 1990 (Box 47)
      - Recommendations for admission, 1988-1990 (Box 47)
    - U.S.A. Votes, 1988-1990 (Box 47)
    - Vaughn, Tricia, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 47)
    - Voorhees, Richard, 1988-1989 (Box 47)
    - General Correspondence:
      - W, 1992 (Box 47)
      - Written but not sent, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Wall Street Journal: Albert Hunt, 1991 (Box 47)